<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Designed by Veterans]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Designed by Veterans]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 03:43:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Waza Media - Make it Designed by Veterans]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Waza Media - Make it Designed by Veterans</h1><p>-- Media Production and Interaction Design Under the Same Roof --At my company, WazaMedia, we create engaging visual and interactive media products that focus on creative storytelling through the use of multiple mediums, and emphasize the human factor behind amazing products and services.Our vision is a changed media landscape. We believe the way your audience interacts with your message is just as important as developing the message itself. We make our content available across the vast array of devices we use, and deliver it in unique interfaces that allow the user to experience the message.My partner Kyle Ramirez and I were both journalists and U.S. Marines. As great friends and collaborators, we have set out to advance the media industry's storytelling capabilities through development and thought leadership. Our company is the outpouring of our combined 16-years of experience in the Marines.We are obsessed with change and stories that help illustrate the human condition. A large part of WazaMedia's culture is studying how emerging media technology and practices are affecting public communication standards and ways of life. It is with these discoveries that we approach each project, and delivers each design.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1510b04f-e158-4b48-868a-f7fb0a37edfe.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1510b04f-e158-4b48-868a-f7fb0a37edfe.png</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0bdc78c3-b703-4e46-bd5a-9cb7fc88b1f3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 03:43:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>